crestock.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy - Crestock.com | Royalty-Free Stock Photos & Vector Illustrations

| 

## Introduction

Crestock Corporation ("Crestock") recognizes the importance of privacy and the sensitivity of Personal Information (defined below). Crestock is committed to protecting any Personal Information that it holds. This Privacy Policy outlines how Crestock manages your Personal Information and safeguards your privacy.

Crestock's Privacy Policy does not apply to information about business entities that carry on business as corporations, partnerships or in other forms of association. Crestock does, however, protect the confidentiality of such information in accordance with the law and Crestock's own policies.

Your initial and continued use of the Crestock website (the "Website") indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Since Crestock regularly reviews all of its privacy policies and procedures, Crestock may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy regularly. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH CRESTOCK'S PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE.

## Personal Information

According to the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ in Canada, and for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means information about an identifiable individual, (e.g. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information), but does not include the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization.

## Children

Crestock does not intend to either solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of eighteen (18) ("Children"). Children are not authorized to use this site unsupervised and are not authorized to register for an account or submit any personal information to Crestock. By using the Website, and/or registering with Crestock for an account, you warrant that you are 18 years of age or older.

## Consent

In most cases, your consent to provide Crestock with your Personal Information (and/or any other information) will be implied through your conduct with it (e.g. speaking with Crestock's staff) or by using the Website (e.g. registering on the Website). In the event that Crestock requires more detailed information, Crestock will request your consent.

## Identifying Purposes - The Personal Information Crestock Collects and How and Why It Collects It

In the event that Crestock does collect Personal Information, it only collects that which is necessary to provide services to you and administer its client and billing databases. Crestock collects information only by lawful and fair means and not in an unreasonably intrusive way. Below are some examples of how Crestock may collect and use your Personal Information (and/or any other information):

  1. **Client Registration:** In order to use Crestock's images, as a "Member" or to conduct a transaction through the Website, you will need to provide Crestock with your contact information and (in some cases) a credit card number so that it can process your request and administer its client and billing databases. Crestock only uses credit card numbers to process a transaction; Crestock does not keep credit card numbers on file. Once you have registered, Crestock may contact you by telephone to confirm your registration. Crestock may also distribute newsletters and other promotional materials that provide the latest information from Crestock and which Crestock believes may be of interest to its registrants. If you wish not to receive such information and materials, you may request to be removed from Crestock's newsletter and promotional materials list.
  2. **Cookies:** Crestock automatically sends a tiny text file called a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of information that your computer shows to Crestock's server whenever you visit the Website. The cookie saves you from having to register and log in every time you return to the Website. Cookies enable the Website to recognize information you have given to Crestock previously, and allow you to participate in the forums and comment on our blog, maintain collections, use a shopping cart, conduct Website transactions and download images from the Website for commercial reproduction. As the Website evolves, Crestock will be able to provide you with many additional levels of service based on its ability to recognize you via your cookie. Crestock's use of the cookie is limited to your activities within the Website and does not have any other effect on your computer or your other activities on the Internet. Crestock does not disclose information in your cookie to other parties.
  3. **Statistical Data & Service Improvement:** Crestock regularly compiles statistical data on clients' Website activity. This data is used to enable Crestock to improve clients' experience on the Website and may be used in future to improve the relevance of the Website for each client by providing clients with products and services that reflect their needs. As an example, Crestock may compile information and create reports in connection with the most used search terms and review the search terms submitted by users of the Website. Crestock may also use this data to help diagnose problems with its server and for systems administration purposes.

## Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention

Crestock does not use or disclose Personal Information for purposes other than those for which it was collected. Also, Crestock retains Personal Information only for as long as it is needed. Certain Personal Information (and/or any other information) may be disclosed to third party contractors solely for the purpose of processing or answering your request(s) including Crestock's representatives, subsidiaries, affiliates and authorized payment processors. Under certain circumstances, Crestock will disclose your Personal Information:

  1. when Crestock is required or authorized by law to do so;
  2. when you have consented to the disclosure, either in writing or through your conduct;
  3. if Crestock engages a third party to provide administrative services to it (e.g. computer back-up services or archival file storage);
  4. as a part of any business merger, sale of the assets of Crestock or acquisition as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which Personal Information would be transferred as part of Crestock's business assets; or
  5. if the information is already publicly known.

Crestock does not, however, transfer, sell or otherwise disclose any of your Personal Information (and/or any other information) to any third party to enable them to market their products and services to you.

If you live in the EU and are subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have the right to edit, update, access, or transfer your personal information, or to delete your personal information if you are terminating your registration with Crestock.

## Access to Your Personal Information

You may ask Crestock for access to your Personal Information. All requests must be in writing and addressed to Crestock's Privacy Officer. A small administrative charge may apply, depending on the request.

Your rights to access your Personal Information are not absolute. Crestock may deny access when:

  1. denial of access is required or authorized by law;
  2. information relates to existing or anticipated legal proceedings against you;
  3. when granting you access would have an unreasonable impact on other people's privacy;
  4. when to do so would prejudice negotiations with you; or
  5. to protect Crestock's rights and property.

If Crestock denies your request for access to Personal Information, it will explain why.

## Accuracy - Updating Your Information

If Crestock has Personal Information about you and your Personal Information has changed or is inaccurate, please inform Crestock so that it can make any necessary changes.

## Safeguards

Crestock takes all reasonable precautions to ensure that your Personal Information (and/or any other information) is kept safe from loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Among the steps taken to protect your information are:

  1. premises security;
  2. restricted file access to Personal Information;
  3. technological safeguards like security software and firewalls to deter hacking or unauthorized computer access; and
  4. internal passwords and security policies.

Given the evolving nature of the Internet, Crestock cannot guarantee that its security measures will be sufficient to protect your Personal Information, however, Crestock will maintain all safeguards it deems reasonably necessary in order to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your Personal Information.

## Communicating with Crestock (e-mails)

Crestock welcomes e-mail communication and uses it frequently. However, e-mail is not a 100% secure medium, and you should be aware of this when contacting Crestock to send Personal Information (and/or any other information). Crestock will not be liable for any Personal Information (and/or any other information) transmitted to it by e-mail.

## Transmission Through Other Countries

You agree and understand that, because of the nature of the Internet, Personal Information (and/or any other information) may be transmitted through other countries that have different rules governing privacy.

## Website Links

At times, the Website may contain links to other sites, which are not governed by this Privacy Policy. To be clear, Crestock is not responsible for Personal Information (and/or any other information) that you disclose to other websites that you may have accessed through the Website.

## Agreements with Third Parties

Aside from Crestock's Authorized Parties, Crestock may enter into agreements with other third parties (e.g. other service providers or suppliers) who may require access to your Personal Information (and/or any other information). Crestock strives to ensure that these third parties also respect your Personal Information (and/or any other information), however, Crestock is not liable for any Third Party misuse of your Personal Information (and/or any other information).

## Requests for Access

If you have any questions regarding Personal Information, please write to Crestock's Privacy Officer:

| By Mail: | Crestock Corporation  
3 Concorde Gate  
Fourth Floor  
Toronto, ON  
Canada M3C 3N7  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
---|---  
By E-mail: | [privacy@crestock.com](mailto:privacy@crestock.com)  
  
v. 2018.05.23
